Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- C, 298311
  - Center for International Studies (Cornell University), undated; 373783 (Box 18)
  - Center for Marxist Education (New York, NY), 1970-1976, undated; 298364 (Box 18)
  - Center for National Security Studies (Washington, DC), 1978; 372915 (Box 18)
  - Center for Policy Research, 1981; 375017 (Box 18)
  - Center for Popular Economics, 1983-1990; 298365 (Box 18)
  - Center for Radical Research, undated; 323971 (Box 18)
  - Center for a Stateless Society, 2011, undated; 423056 (Box 18)
  - Center for Social Action, undated; 374359 (Box 18)
  - Center for Socialist History, 2010-; 323972 (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Popular Culture, undated; 298367 (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions I, 1959-1966, undated; 298368 (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions II, 1959-1966, undated; 298369 (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions III, 1959-1966, undated; 298370 (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions IV, 1959-1966, undated; 298371 (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions V, 1959-1966, undated; 320463 (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions VI, 1959-1966, undated; 320464 (Box 18)
  - Center for United Labor Action, 1971-1979, undated; 298372 (Box 18)
  - Center for Women's Studies and Services, 1981; 379945 (Box 18)
  - Center of Concern, 1979-; 323973 (Box 18)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1988; 423109 (Box 18)
  - Center to Protect Workers' Rights, 1979; 298373 (Box 18)
  - Central America Health Rights Network, 1986; 557843 (Box 121)
  - Central Brooklyn Mobilization for Political Action, 1974; 372916 (Box 19)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors I, 1954-1986, undated; 298374 (Box 19)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors II, 1954-1986, undated; 298375 (Box 19)
  - Central Committee of Correspondence, 1967-1974; 298502 (Box 19)
  - Central Co-operative Wholesale (U.S.), 1933; 298503 (Box 19)
  - Central High School of Needle Trades, 1938; 323974 (Box 19)
  - Central Labor Bodies Conference (political prisoners), 1920; 298504 (Box 19)
  - Central Museum of Labor (Tyovaen Keskusmueo) (Finland), 1990-; 304353 (Box 19)
  - Central Organization of U.S. Marxist-Leninists I, 1974-1979; 298505 (Box 19)
  - Central Organization of U.S. Marxist-Leninists II, 1974-1979; 298506 (Box 19)
  - Central States Co-operative League, 1936-1939, undated; 298507 (Box 19)
  - Centre D'Etudes Socialists (Paris, France), 1969; 298508 (Box 19)
  - Centre for Socialist Education (Nottingham, England), 1968; 298366 (Box 19)
  - Centre International de Recherches sur L'Anarchisme, 1996-2002; 298509 (Box 19)
  - Centre International de Recherches sur L'Anarchisme (Marseille, France), 2002-2003; 298510 (Box 19)
  - Centro Cultural Pablo de la Torriente Brau, 2001-2002; 298511 (Box 19)
  - Centro de Estudios Puertorriquenos (CUNY, Hunter College, New York, NY), 1984; 298512 (Box 19)
  - Centro de la Raza (Seattle, WA), 1980; 298513 (Box 19)
  - Centro de Orientacion y Accion Social, undated; 323975 (Box 19)
  - Centro Studi Libertari G. Pinelli (anarchism), 1986; 298514 (Box 19)
  - Challenge, 1950; 372918 (Box 19)
  - Challenging the Color Line: Confronting the Issues of Race and Class in the Era of Global Capitalism (New York, NY), 2002; 298515 (Box 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America I, 1934-1970; 298516 (Box 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America II, 1934-1970; 298517 (Box 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America III, 1934-1970; 298518 (Box 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States of America IV, 1934-1970; 298519 (Box 19)
  - Chaney Goodman Schwerner Memorial Collection, 1964; 298520 (Box 19)
  - Channel L Working Groups, 1982; 372919 (Box 19)
  - Chardon Press (catalog), 2000; 298522 (Box 19)
  - Charleroi Progressive Co-operative Association (Pennsylvania), 1905-1912; 298521 (Box 19)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company I, 1899-; 304321 (Box 19)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company II, 1899-; 304322 (Box 20)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company III, 1899-; 304323 (Box 20)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company IV, 1899-; 304324 (Box 20)
  - Charles H. Kerr and Company V, 1899-; 304325 (Box 20)
  - Charles Street for Peace, 1968; 374275 (Box 20)
  - Charlottesville Resistance, 1975; 298523 (Box 20)
  - Charney-Trachtenberg Self Defense Committee (NY,NY), undated; 372920 (Box 20)
  - Charter Group for a Pledge of Conscience, 1971-1978; 298524 (Box 20)
  - Chartist International Publications: "British Labor and the Irish Revolution", 1976; 298527 (Box 20)
  - Chartist Publications, 1972-1975, undated; 298525 (Box 20)
  - Chelsea Draft Counseling Service, undated; 373820 (Box 20)
  - Chelsea for Peace, 2007, undated; 372921 (Box 20)
  - Chelsea Neighborhood Association, 1913; 323976 (Box 20)
  - Chelsea Village Lower Manhattan Coalition for Peace, 1970; 298541 (Box 20)
  - Cherry Lawn School, undated; 323977 (Box 20)
  - Chest for Liberation of Workers of Europe, 1938; 298542 (Box 20)
  - Chester Committee for Freedom Now, undated; 323978 (Box 20)
  - Chiapas Media Project, undated; 325714 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Area Draft Resisters I, 1967-1971, undated; 298544 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Area Draft Resisters II, 1967-1971, undated; 298545 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Area Peace and Rally to End the War in Vietnam, 1966; 373927 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Black Cross, 1972; 298546 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Citizen's Committee on Press and Radio, undated; 298547 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Civil Liberties Committee, undated; 344707 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Committee to Defend the Bill of Rights, 1962, circa 1969; 298548 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Committee to End the War in Viet-Nam, 1966; 373924 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Communist Collective, 1972; 298549 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Council Against Racial and Religious Discrimination, 1943-1944; 298550 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Council for Protection of Foreign Born Workers, undated; 298551 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Joint Defense Committee to Defeat the Smith Act, 1956; 375394 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Journal of Commerce, 1946-1949; 298552 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Labor College, 1934; 323979 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Labor Conference for Peace: Women's Committee, undated; 372922 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Labor Peace Conference, 1950s; 298553 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Legal Defense Committee, undated; 373855 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Peace Council, 1968-1972, undated; 298554 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Peace Society, 1915; 298555 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Religious Task Force on Central America, 1986-1989; 379946 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Revolutionary League, undated; 379947 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Student (University of Chicago), 1946; 298556 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Trade Union College (course schedule), 1924-1925; 298557 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Women's Liberation Union, 1972, undated; 379948 (Box 20)
  - Chicago Workers School, 1934-1949; 298558 (Box 20)
  - Child Study Association of America, 1929; 323980 (Box 20)
  - Children's March for Survival New York Coordinating Committee, 1972; 298561 (Box 20)
  - Children's Socialist Schools Committee (New York), 1910; 323981 (Box 20)
  - Chile Antifascista, 1975; 298562 (Box 20)
  - Chile Center for Education and Development (New York, NY), 1984; 298563 (Box 20)
  - Chile Committee for Human Rights (Washington, DC), 1977; 372923 (Box 20)
  - Chile Defense Committee, 1974; 298564 (Box 20)
  - Chile Labor Information, 1985; 298565 (Box 20)
  - Chile Solidarity Committee, 1973-1977; 298566 (Box 20)
  - Chilean Refugee Community (New York, NY), undated; 299187 (Box 20)
  - China Campaign Committee, undated; 298567 (Box 20)
  - China Features, undated; 298568 (Box 20)
  - Chinatown Co-operative a Workers Controlled Garment Factory, undated; 323982 (Box 20)
  - Chinese Construction Workers Association, 1997; 298569 (Box 20)
  - Chinese People's National Committee for the Defense of Children, 1955; 385308 (Box 20)
  - Chinese Staff and Workers Association (Huaren Zhigong Lianyihui) I, 1991-1997; 298570 (Box 20)
  - Chinese Staff and Workers Association (Huaren Zhigong Lianyihui) II, 1991-1997; 298571 (Box 20)
  - Chinese Staff and Workers Association, 1995-2010 (Box 20)
  - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade I, 1960-1986; 298572 (Box 20)
  - Christian Anti-Communism Crusade II, 1960-1986; 298573 (Box 20)
  - Christian Crusade, 1960-1973; 298574 (Box 21)
  - Christian Nationalist Crusade, undated; 323983 (Box 21)
  - Christian Peace Conference, 1964; 298576 (Box 21)
  - Christian Science Monitor, 1966; 373706 (Box 21)
  - Christian Socialist Fellowship, 1908-1909; 298577 (Box 21)
  - Christians for Socialism I, 1978-1983; 298578 (Box 21)
  - Christians for Socialism II, 1978-1983; 320465 (Box 21)
  - Christopher Street Liberation Day Committee, 1971, undated; 298579 (Box 21)
  - Chung-Hua Min Kuo Kuo Chi Kuan Hsi Yen Chiu So, 1963; 298580 (Box 21)
  - Church League for Industrial Democracy, 1920, undated; 323984 (Box 21)
  - Church League of America, 1969-1984; 298581 (Box 21)
  - Church Peace Mission (U.S.), undated; 298582 (Box 21)
  - Church Peace Union, 1958, undated; 298583 (Box 21)
  - Church Socialist League, 1908; 298584 (Box 21)
  - Church Socialist League (Valparaiso, IN), undated; 298585 (Box 21)
  - Cienfuegos Press, 1976-1982, undated; 298586 (Box 21)
  - Cineaste, 1970s; 298587 (Box 21)
  - Circuit Riders, 1957-1958; 298588 (Box 21)
  - Citigroup (anti), 1987-; 323985 (Box 21)
  - Citizen Action of New York, 2000-2004; 298589 (Box 21)
  - Citizen Labor Energy Coalition, undated; 323986 (Box 21)
  - Citizen Soldier, 1981-; 298590 (Box 21)
  - Citizen Works, 2003; 372924 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Association for the Care of Animals, undated; 323987 (Box 21)
  - Citizens' Campaign Against Napalm, 1967; 373934 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee Against Napalm, undated; 323988 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee Against the Ober Law, undated; 323989 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee Against Vicious Employment Agency Tactics, 1956; 323990 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee for a $1.50 Minimum Hourly Wage in New York, 1962-1963; 298591 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee for Better Race Relations, undated; 298592 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties I, 1961-1965; 298593 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties II, 1966-1969; 298594 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties III, 1970-; 298595 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties IV, undated; 298596 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam, undated; 373705 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee for Reorganization of the Executive Branch of the Government, 1950; 323991 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee for the Repeal of the Lusk Schools Laws, undated; 298597 (Box 21)
  - Citizens' Commission of Inquiry, 1970; 374343 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee on the Fair Labor Standards Act, undated; 323992 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee to Defend the Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, undated; 323993 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee to Elect Simon W. Gerson, undated; 327516 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee to Preserve American Freedom, 1953, undated; 299208 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Committee to Protect the Right of Counsel, undated; 323994 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Committee to Repeal P.R., undated; 375395 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Co-operative Supply Company (by-laws), 1914; 298598 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Emergency Committee in Behalf of the Striking Ladies' Tailors and Custom Dressmakers of the Fifth Avenue Shops, 1930; 304317 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Emergency Conference for Interracial Unity, 1943; 323995 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Emergency Defense Conference (New York, NY), 1952; 298599 (Box 21)
  - Citizens for Kennedy-Fulbright, undated; 334598 (Box 21)
  - Citizens for LaRouche, 1980; 298600 (Box 21)
  - Citizens for Local Democracy, undated; 323996 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Housing Council of New York, 1944-1947, undated; 323997 (Box 21)
  - Citizen's Lobby to End the War, undated; 373779 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Party (U.S.) I, 1979-1981; 298601 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Party (U.S.) II, 1979-1981; 298602 (Box 21)
  - Citizens Party (U.S.), 1982-1984; 298711 (Box 22)
  - Citizens Party (U.S.), undated; 298712 (Box 22)
  - Citizens Party (Wisconsin), 1981; 298713 (Box 22)
  - Citizens to Safeguard the Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, 1947; 298714 (Box 22)
  - Citizens Union of the City of New York I, 1903-1982; 298715 (Box 22)
  - Citizens Union of the City of New York II, 1903-1982; 298716 (Box 22)
  - Citizens Union of the City of New York III, 1903-1982; 298717 (Box 22)
  - Citizens Union of the City of New York IV, 1903-1982; 320498 (Box 22)
  - Citizens United for the Continuation of Class Society, circa 1972; 323998 (Box 22)
  - City Action Committee Against the High Cost of Living, 1934; 298718 (Box 22)
  - City Affairs Committee of New York, 1930-1939, undated; 298719 (Box 22)
  - City College Marxist Discussion Group, 1963; 298720 (Box 22)
  - City Club of New York, 1914-1972; 298721 (Box 22)
  - City Fusion Party, 1933, undated; 412273 (Box 22)
  - City of Gary Fair Employment Practice Commission, undated; 422883 (Box 23)
  - City Life, 1986; 298722 (Box 22)
  - City Lights Books, 2008-; 351035 (Box 22)
  - City of Boston Employee's Credit Union, 1915; 323999 (Box 22)
  - City of Hope, 1951; 324000 (Box 22)
  - City of Leeds Labour Party, 1936; 298723 (Box 22)
  - City University of New York (CUNY): Center for Lesbian and Gay Studies, undated; 298724 (Box 22)
  - City University of New York (CUNY): Center for Labor, Community and Policy Studies, 2006-; 298725 (Box 22)
  - City University of New York (CUNY): Center for Worker Education, 1997; 298726 (Box 22)
  - City Wide Association of Day Care Parents Inc. (New York, NY), 1972; 298727 (Box 22)
  - City Wide Tenants Council, 1938; 298728 (Box 22)
  - City-Wide Manhattan North Coalition (against racism), undated; 298729 (Box 22)
  - City Workers Against Apartheid, undated; 324001 (Box 22)
  - City Workers for Real Change, 2000; 334600 (Box 22)
  - Citywide Coalition to Remove Guiliani, 1999; 324002 (Box 22)
  - Civic Club of Allegheny County: Municipal Planning Committee Bulletin, Jan 15, 1918; 342453 (Box 22)
  - Civil Defense Protest Committee, 1960-1961; 298730 (Box 22)
  - Civil Disobedience Against the Draft, undated; 373838 (Box 22)
  - Civil Liberties Legal Defense Fund, Inc. (Cambridge, MA), 1969-1970, undated; 369431 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Congress (U.S.), 1946-1950; 298731 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Congress (U.S.), 1951-1952; 298732 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Congress (U.S.), 1953-1955; 298733 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Congress (U.S.) I, undated; 320499 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Congress (U.S.) II, undated; 320500 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Congress (U.S.): William L. Patterson (pamphlets), 1949-1952, undated; 298734 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Congress of New Jersey, 1940s; 298736 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Defense Committee, 1941, undated; 298735 (Box 22)
  - Civil Rights Federation, 1942; 298737 (Box 22)
  - Clarion Club, undated; 298738 (Box 22)
  - Class Struggle League, 1972-1974; 298739 (Box 22)
  - Clergy and Laity Concerned (CALC), 1980-1983, undated; 324003 (Box 22)
  - Clergy and Laymen Concerned, 1972, undated; 369985 (Box 22)
  - Clergy and Laymen Concerned About Vietnam, 1969-1971, undated; 369986 (Box 22)
  - Clergy and Laymen Concerned About Vietnam (NY,NY), 1967; 372926 (Box 22)
  - Clergy Concerned about Vietnam, undated; 374750 (Box 22)
  - Cleveland Area Peace Action Council, 1970; 374745 (Box 22)
  - Cleveland Women's Liberation, undated; 379949 (Box 22)
  - Clyde Workers Propaganda and Defense Committee, 1918; 298740 (Box 22)
  - Coal Education Project, 1997; 324004 (Box 23)
  - Coal Employment Project, 1986; 298741 (Box 23)
  - Coalicion de Derechos Reproductivas de Filadelfia, undated; 422872 (Box 23)
  - Coalition Against Free Trade, undated; 375396 (Box 23)
  - Coalition Against the American Correctional Association, undated; 324005 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for an Anti-Imperialist Movement, 1968-1969; 298742 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for a Democratic Majority, 1980; 298743 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy (U.S.), 1977-1985; 298744 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for a Non-Nuclear World, 1980; 298745 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for a Nuclear Free Harbor (New York, NY), 1984; 298746 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for a People's Alternative in 1980, 298747 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for a Shorter Work Week, circa 1973; 324006 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for Democratic Socialism, 1980s; 298748 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for the Defense of the Panthers, undated; 324007 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for the Human Rights of Immigrants, 2002; 298749 (Box 23)
  - Coalition for Working Women's Rights, 1989; 324008 (Box 23)
  - Coalition of American Public Employees (CAPE), undated; 324009 (Box 23)
  - Coalition of Concerned Progressive Jews, undated; 324010 (Box 23)
  - Coalition of Graduate Employee Unions, 1997; 298750 (Box 23)
  - Coalition of Grass Roots Women, undated; 298751 (Box 23)
  - Coalition of Immokalee Workers, 2001; 298752 (Box 23)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) (CLUW), 1974-1979; 320501 (Box 23)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) (CLUW), 1980-1991, undated; 298753 (Box 23)
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) (CLUW): New York City, 1974, 1981; 320502 (Box 23)
  - Coalition on National Priorities and Military Policy, undated; 369987 (Box 23)
  - Coalition to Protest the Attica Massacre, undated; 412365 (Box 23)
  - Coalition to Defend the October 20th Freedom Fighters, undated; 324011 (Box 23)
  - Coalition to Greet Ronald "Union Buster" Reagan, undated; 298754 (Box 23)
  - Coalition to Save New York, 1991; 324012 (Box 23)
  - Coalition to Stop U.S. Intervention in the Middle East, circa 1990s; 324013 (Box 23)
  - Code Pink (women against war), 2004, undated; 298755 (Box 23)
  - Coffee Party USA, 2011; 369988 (Box 23)
  - Coleman Defense Committee, undated; 327519 (Box 23)
  - Collecte-Vietnam, undated; 373684 (Box 23)
  - Collectif des centres de Documentation en Histoire et Sociale, 2001; 298756 (Box 23)
  - Collectivist Society (New York, NY), 1903-1934; 298757 (Box 23)
  - Collector Records (Silver Spring, MD), 2000-; 298758 (Box 23)
  - College of the City of New York: Student Strike, 1949; 305655 (Box 23)
  - Colombia Action Committee, undated; 324014 (Box 23)
  - Colombia Solidarity Fund/Center, 2001, undated; 372929 (Box 23)
  - Colorado Organization for Revolutionary Struggle, 1977; 298759 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Anti-Imperialist Movement, undated; 379950 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Defense Committee of Chicago: Emergency National Conference on Columbia, Tennessee Lynch Terror, undated; 298760 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Librarians for Peace, undated; 324015 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Sanctuary, 1969; 374271 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Spectator, 1968; 373824 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Strike Committee, 1968; 298761 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Strike Coordinating Committee, 1968; 298762 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Student Mobilization, 1969; 374267 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Student Solidarity Network, 2000-; 324016 (Box 23)
  - Columbia University, 1968; 324017 (Box 23)
  - Columbia University Forum, 1966; 373710 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Vietnam Summer, 1967; 373951 (Box 23)
  - Columbia Women's Liberation, 1970, undated; 324018 (Box 23)
  - Combahee River Collective (Boston feminists), undated; 324019 (Box 23)
  - Come! Unity Press, 1975-1977; 298763 (Box 23)
  - Comite Central Socialista de Euzkadi, 1945; 298764 (Box 23)
  - Comite d'Action Antifasciste et de Vigilance, 1934; 298765 (Box 23)
  - Comite d'Aide a la Resistance Espagnole, undated; 324020 (Box 23)
  - Comite de Soutien aux Refugies Politiques, undated; 324021 (Box 23)
  - Comite Feminino de White Plains, undated; 298766 (Box 23)
  - Comite For a New Colombia, undated; 372930 (Box 23)
  - Comite' Francais de Solidarite' avec les Victimes de la Repression au Perou, undated; 305547 (Box 23)
  - Comite Movimiento de Izquierda Nacional Puertorriqueno, 1950-1983; 298767 (Box 23)
  - Comite pour la Defense d'Ahmed Ben Bella et des autres Victimes de la Repression en Algerie, 1968; 298768 (Box 23)
  - Comite Pro-Libertad De Presas Politicas, undated; 351048 (Box 23)
  - Comite Unido para el 1 de Mayo, undated; 298769 (Box 23)
  - Commentator Collective (anti-imperialism), 1976; 298770 (Box 23)
  - Commerce and Industry Association of New York, undated; 298771 (Box 23)
  - Commission de L'Europe Centrale et Orientale, 1958; 298772 (Box 23)
  - Commission of Enquiry into the Conditions of Political Prisoners, 1933-1936; 298773 (Box 23)
  - Commission of International Association of Democratic Lawyers, 1952; 298774 (Box 23)
  - Commission of Inquiry into Charges Made Against Leon Trotsky in the Moscow Trials, 1978, undated; 298775 (Box 23)
  - Commission on a Just and Durable Peace, 1945; 298776 (Box 23)
  - Commission on Campus Government and Student Dissent of the American Bar Association, 2002, undated; 298777 (Box 23)
  - Commission on Interracial Cooperation, 1935-1939; 298778 (Box 23)
  - Commission on the Rights, Liberties and Responsibilities of the American Indian, 1961; 298779 (Box 23)
  - Commission on World Peace of the Methodist Church, 1941-1948; 298891 (Box 23)
  - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace I, 1940-1961; 298889 (Box 23)
  - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace II, 1941-1960; 298890 (Box 24)
  - Committee Against Academic Repression (New York, NY), 1969; 298892 (Box 24)
  - Committee Against Jim Crow in Military Service and Training, 1949; 298893 (Box 24)
  - Committee Against Repression in Italy, 1980; 324022 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a 1966 May Day Rally, 373926 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, 1950, undated; 298894 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1962, undated; 298895 (Box 24)
  - Committee to Defend Carlos Feliciano, 1971, undated; 412360 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Free Mozambique, 1973; 298896 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Labor Party (Boston, MA), 1936; 298897 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Labor Party (U.S.), 1970; 298898 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Just Peace in the Middle East, 1971-1975, undated; 372932 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a New Direction for U.S.-Korea Policy, undated; 324023 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Nuclear-Free Island (Staten Island, NY), undated; 298899 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a People's Bicentennial May Day, 1976; 298900 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Revolutionary Socialist Party, 1976; 298901 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Socialist Program, 1956; 298902 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Town Meeting, undated; 374331 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Abortion Rights and Against Sterilization Abuse (New York, NY), 1978-; 298903 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Absolute Revolution, undated; 324024 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Action Research on the Intelligence Community, 1974, undated; 379951 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Aid to Bulgarian Anti-Fascists, undated; 334778 (Box 24)
  - Committee for a Unified Independent Party, 2002-2004, undated; 372933 (Box 24)
  - Committee for an Adequate Minimum Wage for Office Workers, 1940; 298904 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Boycott Against Japanese Aggression, 1940s; 298905 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Citizenship Rights, 1942; 324025 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Constitutional Government, 1958; 298906 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Cooperation with the New South, undated; 298907 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Cultural Freedom, undated; 324026 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Cyprus Affairs, 1946; 298908 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Defense of Public Education, 1941; 298909 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Democratic Rights in the U.S.A. (London), 1961-1962; 298910 (Box 24)
  - Committee for Democratic Palestine, undated; 327517 (Box 24)